click2mail.com 2019-05-26

# Click2Mail Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. Click2Mail, a trade name of C2M LLC, maintains strict customer information privacy policies and uses state of the art technologies to safeguard customer information and communications from unauthorized intrusions. We do not disclose your customer information to third parties who want to market products to you and we always consider your mailing lists and documents to be your private information and protect them accordingly. The following Privacy Policy sets forth Click2Mail's commitment to the protection of our customers' information. 

Click2Mail complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from European Union and Switzerland to the United States, respectively. Click2Mail has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles (the "Principles") of Notice; Choice; Accountability for Onward Transfer; Security; Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation; Access; and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit [ https://www.privacyshield.gov/](https://www.privacyshield.gov/)

This Privacy Policy covers Click2Mail and applies to all customer information that Click2Mail obtains when a customer registers for or uses a Click2Mail online service, including visiting a Click2Mail owned and controlled web site (a "Click2Mail Web Site"). Top Level Domains (TLDs) covered by this Privacy Policy are: Click2Mail.com and Click2EDDM.com. 

From time to time Click2Mail may offer special promotions, contests or other unique marketing efforts which would be governed by their own specific terms and conditions. By choosing to participate in any such marketing effort you consent to the terms and conditions specific to such marketing effort taking precedence over this Privacy Policy, except that to the extent there is any conflict between such specific terms and the Principles, the Principles shall govern as may be required by the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Frameworks. 

Customer Information 

Online privacy concerns focus on the use and protection of customer information which a customer reasonably expects to be kept private. "Customer information" is information which can be associated with a specific individual or entity, including, for example, a customer's name, address, telephone number, email address, financial information and information about online activities that are directly linked to the Customer. As is common practice, we collect customer information, such as name, address, telephone number, credit card information and a variety of other information in the course of providing products and services to a customer and billing a customer. 

Information collected and stored automatically 

During the course of your use of the Click2Mail Web Site and internet services, we automatically track and store certain information about your visit. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our site or not), what browser you are using, and your IP address. We use this information in the normal operation of the Click2Mail Web Site and we may disclose or use this information but only on an aggregated basis. We do not use this information to identify you personally without your express consent. See information regarding cookie usage below. 

Collection and Use 

Click2Mail will collect and use your customer information for the purposes for which you submitted it to the Click2Mail Web Site. As part of the process of providing you with our products and services we may transfer your information to certain vendors acting on our behalf in connection with providing Click2Mail's products and services, each of which is required to use and safeguard your information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy and the Principles. Click2Mail is liable for appropriate onward transfers of personal data to third parties. In addition we use your information for billing purposes, to anticipate and resolve problems with your service, and to create products and services that better meet your needs. Click2Mail may contact you from time to time by means of e-mail, postal mail or by other available means regarding the service for which you are registered. 

Disclosure 

Click2Mail will not sell, trade, rent or disclose to third parties any of your customer information -- including customer names and addresses -- without your consent, unless clearly specified otherwise in this Privacy Policy. Before your customer information is (a) to be disclosed to a non-agent third party, or (b) to be used for a purpose other than the purpose for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by you, Click2Mail will provide you with the opportunity to exercise your choice to opt-out. Click2Mail reserves the right to use or share your information to respond to duly authorized information requests of governmental authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements, or where required by law or in the vital interests of a customer such as when life or health are at stake. Note that Click2Mail is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC). We may also provide your information to a third party in connection with the sale, assignment, or other transfer of the business of Click2Mail to which the information relates, in which case we will require any such buyer to agree to treat your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

Security 

Click2Mail has implemented technology and security features and strict policy guidelines to safeguard the privacy of your customer information from unauthorized access or improper use, and we continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available. 

E-mail and Postal Mail Contents 

Click2Mail will not read or disclose to third parties private postal or electronic communications that you transmit using Click2Mail services except as required to operate the service or as otherwise authorized by law (see "Disclosure" section above). We consider your mailing lists and documents to be your private information. All document and list files you submit will be used solely to provide you with Click2Mail's products and services and in compliance with this Privacy Policy. 

Data Center and Production Center Security 

Click2Mail's physical facilities are very secure. Access to our data center and our production areas is granted to select employees only and limited by electronic badge entry. Our data center and all production facilities are also monitored with surveillance cameras. 

Improper Conduct 

Click2Mail may also use customer information to investigate and help prevent potentially unlawful activity or activity that threatens the network or otherwise violates our Terms of Service. 

Collection of Information by Third Party Sites 

Our policy addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information on other third party sites, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of your personal information. In the case of dealers and resellers of Click2Mail services or Click2Mail co-branded services, we exercise commercially reasonable efforts to cause such persons to honor the provisions of this Privacy Policy, but we cannot be held responsible if they fail to do so. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of all third party sites to which you disclose your personal information. 

Cookies 

Like most web sites, Click2Mail makes use of session "cookies." Cookies are files written to a user's hard disk and read by server programs to inform a web site if the user has previously visited that site. We use cookies to continually enhance your Click2Mail experience. 

Changes to Click2Mail's Privacy Policy 

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do update it we will make the updated policy available on this page 

Comments or Concerns 

You have the right to review and correct or delete any of the personal information which we have collected from you by contacting us at the address below. 

Any customer, including any European Union or Swiss citizens, with any comments or concerns about this Privacy Policy or our collection or use of your personal information or who would like to obtain a copy of or correct or amend any personal information may contact us at: [webmaster@Click2Mail.com](mailto:webmaster@click2mail.com). 

EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield 

In compliance with the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Principles,Click2Mail commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Click2Mail at: [webmaster@Click2Mail.com](mailto:webmaster@click2mail.com)

Click2Mail has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Privacy Shield Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [ https://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/](https://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers) for more information and to file a complaint. 

Under certain limited conditions, it may be possible for EU or Swiss individuals to seek redress from the Privacy Shield Panel, a binding arbitration mechanism. 

Last updated: 5 December, 2018
